{
	"tf" : [
        {
            "name" : "tf1",
            "question" : "JSP is a technology that was based on a famous language, Java.",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "True"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "False"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "a"
        },
        {
            "name" : "tf2",
            "question" : "JavaServer files together with HTML files which includes tags that has the java source code that will provide static content.",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "True"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "False"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "b"
        },
        {
            "name" : "tf3",
            "question" : "JSP or JavaServer Pages is easy and will give the programmers/developers to create websites and applications in a faster way..",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "True"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "False"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "a"
        },
        {
            "name" : "tf4",
            "question" : "JSP has only one platform.",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "True"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "False"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "b"
        },
        {
            "name" : "tf5",
            "question" : "Declaration Tag allows a developer in declaring variables or even methods.",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "True"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "False"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "a"
        },
        {
            "name" : "tf6",
            "question" : "The data from HTML cannot be pass straight into a JavaBean.",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "True"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "False"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "b"
        },
        {
            "name" : "tf7",
            "question" : "As the word itself declarations Is the one declaring one or more variables or methods which you can be used to cod in Java.",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "True"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "False"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "a"
        },
        {
            "name" : "tf8",
            "question" : "JSP Expression was an element which has no scripting language that is being monitored.",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "True"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "False"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "b"
        },
        {
            "name" : "tf9",
            "question" : "A JSP comments is the one that marks text, which the container of the JSP must not be noticed or simple must be ignored.",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "True"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "False"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "a"
        },
        {
            "name" : "tf10",
            "question" : "JSP comment not important , when you want to describe or give meaning to a part of your JSP.",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "True"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "False"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "b"
        }
    ]
}